[HAPPY]😊 gentlemen you
[HAPPY]😊 Bye.
[EPIC]⚡ consider this a revolve or holds six bullets not eight
[EPIC]⚡ Then stop.
[EPIC]⚡ video.
[EPIC]⚡ by the state of May, and I hear my order you deserve two life sentences back to bed. One for each of your victims. So be it!
[EPIC]⚡ send you here for life.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 That's it.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Yes, I'm out! Yes, I'm out!
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ 7.
[EPIC]⚡ Do it.
[EPIC]⚡ I didn't touch that.
[EPIC]⚡ I'm gonna fit right here.
[EPIC]⚡ I
[EPIC]⚡ head out.
[EPIC]⚡ There are places where they aren't moving out of stone. There's something inside. There's hand time.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Hope. You'll take some of my friend. Hope. It's a dangerous thing. Damn it, Duke, Brian. You're putting me behind. Hope and travel man and the same. You better be sick, or dead, and there are kids you got. I'm better than you, so that I get. Oh, my, holy God. As he comes down to a simple choice.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you very much.
[EPIC]⚡ You get this, you die. Get busy living. I'll get busy dying. That's damn right.